Hello friends, how are you? I hope you are doing
well. Today we will learn how to make
ICICI Lord's first party
insurance from CSC. First of all, the first
option google2CSC will come up,
click on it. My account is logged
in here, so you guys are logged in,
let's log it out first of all,
we have logged it out from here, now log in again so that
you guys understand clearly.
Here you have to enter your CSC ID password
and fill the captcha very carefully.
After filling the captcha,
click on the sign in option. Click on the sign in
option. Your digital service
portal will open after logging in.
This dashboard will come in front of you. Your
CSC dashboard will come after that.
Go to the search option and type
ICICI Lord here. As soon as you search, you will
see here that the motor third party wrap will
come up. Click on that as soon as you
click on that, this is the portal of CSC which is of
ICS Lomber along with CSC. This is a
bit heavy portal and a bit slow,
so you will have to wait a
little while it gets recreated.  It takes time to load the
page. As soon as this page is loaded,
after loading it will open in front of you,
as it has just come, in this you will find two
wheeler, four wheeler, PCB, passenger carriage
vehicle, GCB, goods carry vehicle, which is a vehicle of similar make,
like pickup,
miscellaneous like tractor,
whatever it is, all this comes under miscellaneous
and health, so we will
start here, we will make insurance of a bike two wheeler,
package here and TP
third party, TP means third party, so to
make a package, we will make first party, so we will
click on first package, here the
registration number of your bike, which will be the
registration number, has to be entered here, so let's
enter here
and click on get RTO details,
as soon as you click on get RTO details, the
year of manufacturing of the vehicle will come,
everything will be auto filled, but
what to do here, whatever model of bike you choose, enter the
model of the bike a little carefully
because sometimes some
alternates keep coming from RTO and there will be some model on your RC
here and some like  Right now we have
Passion Pro and here Passion X
Expo has come, so our model is FPR i3s, so we
will select FPR i3s here, as soon as we select it,
what is there in it,
after selecting it, you will also get the ID of that car and
what is its ex-showroom price, both of them will be
shown here, after that click below
and you don't have to do much,
click on Add Previous Policy,
when was your previous policy started and when did it expire, for example, it was on
23-14
January 2023 and it ended on 13th, so
we do not know
how much NCB was received in the previous policy, hence we will keep it
zero, we will do it on the gate code,
as soon as you enter the gate code,
your total premium will be shown here including
GST, do a view premium
backup here, in this you can see everything, in which
1243 your money was invested, so how much did you pay, how much did you pay, how much did you spend
on third party, what is the
basic premium,
how much did you get NCB % of this  You have to
close it. After checking everything,
click on proceed. As soon as you
click on proceed, carefully match all these details with yourself.
Then
additional previous policy details will appear.
Which company was your previous policy from and
what is its policy number, you have to select it here. For example, let
us select here
that our previous policy
was from AAS Lombard only and since we are
not clear on that NCB, we will
assume NCB as zero this time and will
not give NCV on our own. We have
selected ICSA Lombard here and
our previous policy, the policy number on the previous policy
which has expired, will be there.
That policy number of the insurance has to be
entered here. For example, let us
enter the previous policy number here. After entering it here, you will
see below that there is a KYC detail.
Click on KYC. Here you have three options -
Aadhar, PAN and others. The best and quick one is
KYC through PAN card. So,
enter your PAN number here.
After entering the PAN number  The date of birth which will be on the PAN,
and by selecting the date of birth here, you have to
fill the same date of birth here
because many customers have different dates,
so the date of birth which will be on the PAN,
you have to fill it here and click on submit,
so click on submit here, like for a
few days you will get the option of please wait,
after that see, the customer central KYC which is
C KYC, all this detail has been
taken automatically, then what you have to do is
click on check on proceed, come down and check your details
mobile number email ID, whether it is correct or
not, if everything is correct then
click on generate proposal, like
click on generate proposal,
after that you have to wait for the question,
total premium will come here, then
click on buy now buy now, this will come on your digital
service payment option, here you have to
enter the password which you used to login for CSC, validate that,
after that
enter your wallet pin here and make the payment, the payment will be
successful, wait for some time  Like
wait, congratulations will appear here,
you have successfully generated a
policy, please find the below details below,
how much is your total premium, it is
shown here, policy
number, when is the policy starting, if you have done it
today then it is starting from 281 2024,
when will it end, the policy will end one day less on 271
2025, there will be an arrow here,
click on it below the premium, please wait option will appear,
click for a while, this policy
paper will start downloading and
after downloading, here it is, it is downloaded,
now let us open it, let us
open it, this is your Lombard
first party bike insurance,
here you have to check everything carefully,
how is it, it will
give you the premium breakup, see here, the
agency code will appear below, your agency code is CSCSPV,
next agency name is CSC
Government Service India, agent contact
number and agent contact person, which is your
name